<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- CVS_BerberCS_Text -->
<!-- Author: thecrazyscotsman -->
<!-- DateCreated: 12/18/2017 6:28:03 PM -->
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<!-- Garama-->
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CIVILIZATION_GARAMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Garama</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CIVILIZATION_GARAMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Garama city-state</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CIVILIZATION_GARAMA_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Garaman</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CITY_NAME_GARAMA" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Garama</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_LEADER_TRAIT_GARAMA_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Garama Suzerain Bonus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_LEADER_TRAIT_GARAMA_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_Food] Food on Oases and adjacent land tiles. +1 [ICON_Food] Food on land tiles two away.</Text>
		</Replace>

		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_GARAMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Garama was the capital of the Garamantian Kingdom. The Garamantes were a Berber tribe who developed an advanced civilization in ancient southwestern Libya. They used an elaborate underground irrigation system, and founded prosperous Berber kingdoms or city-states in the Fezzan area of Libya, in the Sahara desert. They were a local power between 500 BC and 700 AD.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_GARAMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Garamantes were probably present as tribal people in the Fezzan by 1000 BC. They appear in the written record for the first time in the 5th century BC: according to Herodotus, they were "a very great nation" who herded cattle, farmed dates, and hunted the Troglodytae ("cave-dwellers") who lived in the desert, from four-horse chariots. Roman depictions describe them as bearing ritual scars and tattoos. Tacitus wrote that they assisted the rebel Tacfarinas and raided Roman coastal settlements. According to Pliny the Elder, Romans eventually grew tired of Garamantian raiding and Lucius Cornelius Balbus captured 15 of their settlements in 19 BC. In 202, Septimius Severus captured the capital city of Garama.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_GARAMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Garamantes were farmers and merchants. Their diet consisted of grapes, figs, barley, and wheat. They traded wheat, salt and slaves in exchange for imported wine and olive oil, oil lamps and Roman tableware. According to Strabo and Pliny, the Garamantes quarried amazonite in the Tibesti Mountains.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_GARAMA_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>By around 150 AD the Garamantian kingdom (in today's central Libya (Fezzan), principally along the still existing Wadi al-Ajal), covered 180,000 square kilometres in modern-day southern Libya. It lasted from about 400 BC to 600 AD. The decline of the Garamantian culture may have been connected to worsening climatic conditions, or overuse of water resources. What is desert today was once fairly good agricultural land and was enhanced through the Garamantian irrigation system 1,500 years ago. As fossil water is a non-renewable resource, over the six centuries of the Garamantian kingdom, the ground water level fell. The kingdom declined and fragmented.</Text>
		</Replace>

		<!-- Sale-->
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Salé</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Salé city-state</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_ADJECTIVE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Salé</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_CITY_NAME_SALE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Salé</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_LEADER_TRAIT_SALE_NAME" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Salé Suzerain Bonus</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_CVS_LEADER_TRAIT_SALE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Your Naval Raider units gain an extra attack.</Text>
		</Replace>

		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Salé is a city in north-western Morocco, on the right bank of the Bou Regreg river, opposite the national capital Rabat, for which it serves as a commuter town. Founded in about 1030 by Arabic-speaking Berbers, the Banu Ifran, it later became a haven for pirates as an independent republic before being incorporated into Alaouite Morocco.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The Phoenicians established a settlement called Sala, later the site of a Roman colony, Sala Colonia, on the south side of the Bou Regreg estuary. It is sometimes confused with Salé, on the opposite north bank. Salé was founded in about 1030 by Arabic-speaking Berbers who apparently cultivated the legend that the name was derived from that of Salah, son of Ham, son of Noah.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>	The Banu Ifran Berber dynasty began construction of a mosque about the time the city was founded.[9] The present-day Great Mosque of Salé was built during the 12th-century reign of the Almohad sultan Abu Yaqub Yusuf, although not completed until 1196. During the 17th century, Rabat was known as New Salé, or Salé la neuve (in French), as it expanded beyond the ancient city walls to include the Chellah, which had become a fortified royal necropolis under the rule of Abu Yaqub Yusuf's son, Abu Yusuf Yaqub al-Mansur. In September 1260, Salé was raided and occupied by warriors sent in a fleet of ships by King Alfonso X of Castile.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_4" Language="en_US">
			<Text>In the 17th century, Salé became a haven for the Barbary pirates, among them Moriscos turned corsair, who even formed a Republic of Salé. Salé pirates (the well-known "Salé Rovers") roamed the seas, and cruised the shipping routes between Atlantic colonial ports and Europe, seizing American and European ships and selling their crews into slavery. Despite the legendary reputation of the Salé corsairs, their ships were actually based across the river in Rabat, called "New Salé" by the English. The city of Salé was bombarded by the French Admiral Isaac de Razilly on 20 July 1629 with a fleet composed of the ships Licorne, Saint-Louis, Griffon, Catherine, Hambourg, Sainte-Anne, Saint-Jean; 3 corsair ships were destroyed.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_5" Language="en_US">
			<Text>During the decades preceding the independence of Morocco, the city was the stronghold of some "national movement" activists. The reading of the "Latif" (a politically charged prayer to God, read in mosques in loud unison) was launched in Salé and relayed in some cities of Morocco. In 1851, Salé was bombarded in retaliation for piracy being practiced by Moroccan ships against European traders.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_6" Language="en_US">
			<Text>A petition against the so-called "Berber Dahir" (a decree that allowed some Berber-speaking areas of Morocco to continue using Berber Law, as opposed to Sharia Law) was given to Sultan Mohamed V and the Resident General of France. The petition and the "Latif" prayer led to the withdrawal and adjustment of the so-called "Berber Decree" of May 1930. The activists who opposed the "Berber Decree" apparently feared that the explicit recognition of the Berber Customary Law (a very secular-minded Berber tradition) would threaten the position of Islam and its Sharia law system. Others saw in opposing the French-engineered "Berber Decree" a means to turn the table against the French occupation of Morocco.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="LOC_PEDIA_CITYSTATES_PAGE_CVS_CIVILIZATION_SALE_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_7" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The widespread storm that was created by the "Berber Dahir" controversy created a somewhat popular Moroccan nationalist elite based in Salé and Fez with strong anti-Berber, anti-West, anti-secularism, and with strong Arab-Islamic inclinations. That episode of Moroccan history was the basis of some of the political awareness that would lead fourteen years later the signing of the Manifest of Independence of Morocco on 11 January 1944 by many "Slawi" activists and leaders. Salé has also been deemed to have been the stronghold of the Moroccan left for many decades, where many leaders have resided.</Text>
		</Replace>
	</LocalizedText>
</GameData>
